{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Demolition Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40207/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40207,"taskName":"Demolition","taskDescription":"Demolish and Remove Structures","xmTaskDescriptor":"Demolition Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1005,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Demolish Structure Structures building pool","textMessagingName":"Demolition","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically a demolition or salvage company. Many builders \u0026 remodelers will remove the old before building the new, but this category is for firms that will handle the removal of the old as a stand-alone project.","rolloverShortDesc":"Used even when not involved in the re-building project.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Demolish and Remove Structures.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"House \u0026 Building Demolition Contractors \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":18,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Demolition","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Demolition","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Demolition Project","urlName":"Demolition","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best House Demolition Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Demolish,Structure,Structures,building,pool,Demolition","emcCategoryOid":-12018,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":514,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40207/":{"taskOID":40207,"originalTaskOID":40207,"setID":514,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4898,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Demolition","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of demolition do you need? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6440,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Total demolition","answerDisplayText":"Total demolition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4581,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial (selective) demolition","answerDisplayText":"Partial (selective) demolition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6148,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Strip out interior","answerDisplayText":"Strip out interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3145,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Implosion","answerDisplayText":"Implosion","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":856,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Asbestos abatement","answerDisplayText":"Asbestos abatement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2250,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Environmental clean-up","answerDisplayText":"Environmental clean-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4900,"questionDisplayText":"Location of demolition work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs demolition work?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3092,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"House","answerDisplayText":"House","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":798,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Apartment","answerDisplayText":"Apartment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1510,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Commercial building/complex","answerDisplayText":"Commercial building/complex","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4468,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Outbuilding","answerDisplayText":"Outbuilding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1115,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bridge","answerDisplayText":"Bridge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1375,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Chimney","answerDisplayText":"Chimney","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4898,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Demolition","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of demolition do you need? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6440,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Total demolition","answerDisplayText":"Total demolition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4581,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial (selective) demolition","answerDisplayText":"Partial (selective) demolition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6148,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Strip out interior","answerDisplayText":"Strip out interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3145,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Implosion","answerDisplayText":"Implosion","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":856,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Asbestos abatement","answerDisplayText":"Asbestos abatement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2250,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Environmental clean-up","answerDisplayText":"Environmental clean-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6440,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Total demolition","answerDisplayText":"Total demolition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4581,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial (selective) demolition","answerDisplayText":"Partial (selective) demolition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6148,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Strip out interior","answerDisplayText":"Strip out interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3145,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Implosion","answerDisplayText":"Implosion","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":856,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Asbestos abatement","answerDisplayText":"Asbestos abatement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2250,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Environmental clean-up","answerDisplayText":"Environmental clean-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4900,"questionDisplayText":"Location of demolition work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs demolition work?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3092,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"House","answerDisplayText":"House","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":798,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Apartment","answerDisplayText":"Apartment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1510,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Commercial building/complex","answerDisplayText":"Commercial building/complex","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4468,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Outbuilding","answerDisplayText":"Outbuilding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1115,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bridge","answerDisplayText":"Bridge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1375,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Chimney","answerDisplayText":"Chimney","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3092,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"House","answerDisplayText":"House","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":798,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Apartment","answerDisplayText":"Apartment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1510,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Commercial building/complex","answerDisplayText":"Commercial building/complex","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4468,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Outbuilding","answerDisplayText":"Outbuilding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1115,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bridge","answerDisplayText":"Bridge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1375,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Chimney","answerDisplayText":"Chimney","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}